{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"1","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?","answer":"\u0d07. \u0d0e\u0d02. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"2","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d27\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"3","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"4","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d7d-\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"5","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"6","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d48\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7c "},{"q_number":"7","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02-\u0d35\u0d28\u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"8","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1f\u0d3f.\u0d0e. \u0d2e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"9","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"10","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"11","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"20"},{"q_number":"12","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"9"},{"q_number":"13","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \r\n"},{"q_number":"14","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e?","answer":"141"},{"q_number":"15","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e?","answer":"140"},{"q_number":"16","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2f "},{"q_number":"17","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d13. \u0d10. \u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"18","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d40\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f?","answer":"7 \u0d24\u0d35\u0d23"},{"q_number":"19","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d32\u0d39\u0d33 "},{"q_number":"20","question":"\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02?","answer":"1941"},{"q_number":"33","question":"\u0d0e.\u0d21\u0d3f. 1000\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"34","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d43\u0d25\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b, \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"35","question":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e, \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02, \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"36","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e"},{"q_number":"37","question":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d0e.\u0d21\u0d3f. 1206 - 1290"},{"q_number":"38","question":"\u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"1414 - 1451"},{"q_number":"39","question":". '\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\" \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d10\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"40","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"41","question":"\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b\u0d10\u0d2c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"42","question":"\u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"43","question":"\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02\u0d15\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d02\u0d17 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d18 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d41\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d39\u0d7d\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"44","question":"\u0d31\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46"},{"q_number":"45","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d","answer":"1266 - 1287"},{"q_number":"46","question":"'\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\" \u0d05\u0d25\u0d35\u0d3e \u0d26\u0d48\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"47","question":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"48","question":"\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2c\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"49","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35 \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"50","question":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41"},{"q_number":"51","question":"'\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41"},{"q_number":"52","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7c, \u0d24\u0d2c\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41 "},{"q_number":"53","question":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"54","question":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f '\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"55","question":"1398 \u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d7b "},{"q_number":"56","question":"1451\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d32\u0d42\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f "},{"q_number":"57","question":"1526 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d7e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"58","question":"'\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"59","question":"'\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"60","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d37\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28 "},{"q_number":"61","question":"\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41"},{"q_number":"62","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"186","question":"\u0d06\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33 \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n \r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a \r\n"},{"q_number":"187","question":"\u0d0f. \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d 750\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d 32 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d25...."},{"q_number":"492","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"493","question":"\u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"494","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"495","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d24\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"496","question":"\u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 23- \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"497","question":"\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"1674\r\n"},{"q_number":"498","question":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"499","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d39\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d38\u0d41\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d I\r\n"},{"q_number":"500","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d. \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"501","question":"\u0d06\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"502","question":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d08\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"503","question":"\u0d1a\u0d57\u0d38 \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d37\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"504","question":"\u0d16\u0d41\u0d31\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"505","question":"\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"506","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"507","question":"\u0d21\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"508","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"BC.468, \u0d2a\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"509","question":"\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"510","question":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\r\n"},{"q_number":"511","question":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"512","question":"\u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"513","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d24\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"1784\r\n"},{"q_number":"955","question":" \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"956","question":"\u0d1a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"957","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"24"},{"q_number":"958","question":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d37\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d 1857 \u2013 \u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d37\u0d3e II"},{"q_number":"959","question":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46"},{"q_number":"960","question":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d2b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f29. \u0d09\u0d34\u0d35\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"961","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d41"},{"q_number":"962","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1744"},{"q_number":"963","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"964","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d26\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"965","question":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e"},{"q_number":"966","question":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"967","question":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d47\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d35\u0d23 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"968","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"969","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"970","question":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d15\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d42\u0d23\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"971","question":"\u0d28\u0d35\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d26\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d II"},{"q_number":"972","question":"\u0d36\u0d15\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d, AD 78"},{"q_number":"973","question":"\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"974","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f, BC 563"},{"q_number":"975","question":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"976","question":"\u0d07\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d42\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b"},{"q_number":"977","question":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"978","question":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"979","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d38\u0d40\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"980","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"981","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2a\u0d40\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d1f \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"982","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1757"},{"q_number":"983","question":"\u0d06\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"984","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"985","question":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2b\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"986","question":"\u0d39\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d38\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"987","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d, \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d, 119257. \u0d2e\u0d42\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d40\u0d38"},{"q_number":"988","question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"989","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"990","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d09\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"991","question":"2010 \u0d36\u0d15\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1932"},{"q_number":"992","question":"\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"993","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02, BC 483"},{"q_number":"994","question":"\u0d24\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1565"},{"q_number":"995","question":"\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"996","question":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"997","question":"\u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d32\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"13"},{"q_number":"998","question":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"999","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d26\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"16"},{"q_number":"1000","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d02 ?","answer":"1526"},{"q_number":"1001","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d48\u0d35\u0d4d, \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d57\u0d33"},{"q_number":"1002","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d32\u0d42\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1003","question":"\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d1c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41"},{"q_number":"1004","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1005","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d32\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1006","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02"},{"q_number":"1007","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1008","question":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 ?","answer":"606 \u2013 647"},{"q_number":"1009","question":"\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d16\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1010","question":"\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1011","question":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1012","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d15\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1013","question":"\u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02 ?","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d17\u0d43\u0d39\u0d02, BC 483"},{"q_number":"1014","question":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1015","question":"\u0d36\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1016","question":"\u0d14\u0d31\u0d02\u0d17\u0d38\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d57\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1017","question":"\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d35\u0d47\u0d32\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16 ?","answer":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2d \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16"},{"q_number":"1018","question":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2b\u0d48\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1019","question":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1020","question":"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1021","question":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48"},{"q_number":"1022","question":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d37\u0d3e"},{"q_number":"1023","question":"\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1024","question":"\u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"1025","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d37\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1026","question":"\u0d24\u0d31\u0d48\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f, \u0d2a\u0d43\u0d25\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1027","question":"\u0d24\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1028","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"1029","question":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d"},{"q_number":"1030","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d38\u0d41\u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41"}]},"code":"100"}